### MICHAEL BRIAN WARD

FRONT-END DEVELOPER REACT/JS

#### **PROFILE**

I have a very mixed background when it comes to my job experience, but every job I had I received promotions and ended up taking on a leadership role in. I have always taken pride in my work, and for the first time in my life I feel I am where I belong with coding.

#### **CONTACT**

thewardbunch@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/michaelbrian-ward-6494951b2/

(843) 214-3314

2217 N Hwy 17a

Bonneau, SC 29431

### **EXPERIENCE**

# LEAD ELECTRICIAN, ELITE ELECTRIC CO., SUMMERVILLE, SC

JAN 2017-MAR 2020

Ordered materials for jobs, oversaw training of new hires, assigned tasks for workers, kept track of total man hours for job, made sure all work passed inspections. 100% passed inspections rate for term of employment

# PAWN SHOP MANAGER, MONEY MAN PAWN, SUMMERVILLE, SC

APRIL 2012- NOV 2016

Oversaw training for new hires, keeping track of payroll budget, researching items and qualifying loans on said items.

### STORE MANAGER, DOLLAR GENERAL, CROSS, SC

MAY 2009- APRIL 2012

Oversaw payroll budget, ordering merchandise to keep store stocked, training new hires.

# STORE MANAGER, MONEY MAN PAWN, SUMMERVILLE, SC

NOV 2006- MAY 2009

Responsible for training new hires, keeping track of payroll budget, researching items and qualifying loans on said items.

## LEAD ELECTRICIAN, ELITE ELECTRIC CO., SUMMERVILLE, SC

APRIL 1999 - NOV 2006

Ordered materials for jobs, oversaw training of new hires, assigned tasks for workers, kept track of total man hours for job.

## **EDUCATION**

#### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPEMENT

KENZIE ACADEMY, INDIANAPOLIS IN APRIL 2021

## LANGUAGES, OTHER SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Express, Zustand, Bootstrap, MongoDB, APIs, Git, Data Structures, Deployment, RESTful APIs,